

# Nawaf Khaled Al Nujaidy

- 0553555908
- Nawafalnujaidy@gmail.com
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/nawaf-alnujaidy-392751108
- Riyadh

# **Job Description**

Working positively and sincerely, working diligently and always striving to complete tasks at the highest level, experience in dealing with internal and external audiences based on my scientific and practical experience in media and public relations, enjoying continuous learning and working under pressure.

### **Skills**

- Content industry
- Photography
- Managing social media accounts through the buffer program
- leadership
- Effective communication with co-workers

# Languages

- Arabic / mother tongue
- · English/ Excellent

#### **Education**

Bachelor's degree in media and public relations King Saud University 2013

# **Experiences**

- Public Relations Administrator at Al Fozan Trading Company from January 2014 to August 2013"4
- Public Relations Officer of the Ministry of Education / Higher Education from November 2014 to November 2015
- Media and social communication specialist at Fox Advertising Company (Part-time job) from January 2016 until now.
- A medical photographer for the Security Forces Hospital program from June 2020 Until now .

# **Training courses**

- Collaborative training in the Department of Relations and Media at King Saud University in 2013 as a graduation project.
- Management and organization of events from the King Fahd Cultural Center 2018
- New communication skills with Professor Hani Al-Ghafili 2018.

## **Achievements**

- Raising the proposal to fill the wells due to the large number of children falling at that time From Al Fozan Company as part of its social responsibility
- Raising a proposal to monitor community reactions and public opinion on social media through the Buffer program